[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Lin Zai!
How did he end up like this?
I'll go get Dr. He.
Don't get him! Hurry, get Cheng!
How... How did this happen?
He's lost too much blood. It's dangerous.
It's best to give him a transfusion now.
But...
Take my blood. I'm Type O.
Okay, I'll go get ready.
He's stable for now.
But his body is severely weakened.
Whether he survives or not...
depends on his own will.
I'll watch over him.
- Okay. - Lie.
What exactly happened?
Who hurt Lin Zai like this?
Lin Zai needs peace and quiet.
Everyone, please step out.
Lie, take good care of him.
Lin Zai.
You have to pull through.
I'll never leave you again.
Please.
You have to wake up.
[Apocalypse Log 20]
Lin Zai.
You damn well dare to show up?
Lie, stop it!
What are you doing?
Stop hitting him!
Lie!
Stop...
Lin Zai!
You're awake.
It was all voluntary.
Voluntary?
He drained you until you're like this!
He Yao is researching a way to fight zombies.
It's a good thing.
It's my own fault for not being careful.
It's my fault.
I didn't control the amount that was drawn.
No research justifies risking a life.
Lie.
Get out.
Then...
- Lin Zai, get some rest. - Get out.
Child, you can't do anything foolish again.
There are so few of us left,
we can't afford to lose anyone else.
Grandma Qiu, don't worry.
He Yao has always been good to me.
This was just an accident.
When I found you,
you were lying there all alone.
There wasn't a soul around you.
What would've happened if I hadn't returned?
He doesn't value your life at all.
Grandma Qiu, Chen.
I want to talk to Lie alone.
You two go and rest.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
You watched over me all night.
I thought you left.
Why did you come back?
Do you really...
trust him that much?
Enough to let yourself end up like this
just to help him with his experiment?
You clearly...
hated being a test subject.
I even let you go.
Why go this far for him?
If you hadn't woken up, I...
That's not it, Lie.
I'm not doing this for He Yao.
It's for my brother.
Your brother?
To protect me,
my brother was bitten by a zombie.
He's in He Yao's lab.
I saw him.
He Yao said he could turn my brother back into a human.
That's why...
If you wanted to save him, why not tell me?
I thought...
you really wanted to push me away.
And abandon me.
I was just...
I was just afraid that if you found out,
you would stop me.
Lin Zai.
So, you didn't really want to kick me out, did you?
I'm sorry, Lie.
I didn't mean anything I said that day.
From now on, no matter what happens,
you have to tell me.
Don't carry the burden alone anymore.
And don't ever...
push me away again.
Okay.
Brother.
What happened to your face?
It's nothing.
I just fell.
You used to lie to Mom like that when you were little.
Did someone hit you?
You slept for a long time this time.
How do you feel?
Do you feel unwell anywhere?
This...
The dosage this time...
It's not right.
Brother.
What did you do to that immune subject?
This is why you got beaten up, right?
Look at me.
Answer me!
Chang Huan, what are you doing?
He Yao.
What have you done?
You promised me...
that you would keep him safe.
What do you take him for?
A blood bank?
Yes.
And he has to be one.
Without his blood, you'll die.
You'll rot.
You'll become an irrational monster.
Tell me, if I don't treat him as a blood bank,
what should I do?
What else can I do?
Does that give you the right to hurt him like this?
He Yao.
This is wrong.
To me, right and wrong are meaningless now.
I just want you to come back.
You're not the He Yao I know.
The He Yao I know...
He would never do such a thing.
Stop this.
Stop before it's too late.
Please?
There's no going back.
What are you doing?
He Yao!
He Yao, untie me!
You can't keep making these mistakes.
He Yao!
It seems I can't let you stay.
Lie.
You've only just recovered.
Don't overwork yourself.
I'm fine, Granny Qiu.
I feel much better.
You made this?
He certainly did.
This young man is quite capable.
He went out before dawn.
He actually managed to bring back a pheasant.
He also gathered a lot of ingredients.
And traded for a bunch of seasonings.
Wow, it smells so good.
Wow, this smells amazing!
Where did you get a pheasant, kid?
- Let us have a taste. - Don't touch it.
Wow, it smells so good.
Move.
Go get a bowl. Get a bowl.
Go get a bowl. There's enough for everyone.
Thank you, Granny Qiu.
This time, it's perfect in every way.
Who would have thought, in a world like this,
we could still have a meal like this?
All right.
I'll go clean up the pot.
I'll leave things here to you, Lie.
Granny Qiu, won't you have some?
I've already eaten.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
Drink up.
I suddenly think you're kind of cute.
Nonsense.
Just drink it.
I didn't expect the camp to have a place like this.
In this apocalypse, it's like a hidden paradise.
I'll bring you here every day from now on.
Lie.
Remember I told you about saving my brother?
You're still going to cooperate with He Yao's experiment?
He's the only family I have left in this world.
No matter what, I can't give up on him.
Why do you trust He Yao so much?
Because I saw it with my own eyes.
My brother went from a manic state
to slowly calming down.
Sometimes, the way he looks at me...
It's as if he recognizes me.
He just can't speak yet.
But your body...
I'm much better.
I can handle it.
I want to go see my brother.
Okay.
I'll go with you.